{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","address":"4206 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Tzohai Izayano","licenseNumber":"229207","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":null,"establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E610000004F607E6E2C354C01060104C062D4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43932","establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","inspectionDate":"2018-10-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"0","pfcount":"2","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43932","inspectionDate":"10/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"43932","inspectionDate":"10/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under ยง 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \r\n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\r\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\r\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\r\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\r\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\r\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\r\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \r\n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \r\n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\r\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"Covered","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Cool items uncovered on the top shelf of cooler."},{"inspectionid":"43932","inspectionDate":"10/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"Hand sink(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"43932","inspectionDate":"10/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at handsink dishwash area","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Hand sink(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate supply of soap at all hand sinks."},{"inspectionid":"43932","inspectionDate":"10/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in manner that does not contaminate items"}]},{"inspectionid":"42949","establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","inspectionDate":"2018-07-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"114","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"42364","establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","inspectionDate":"2018-05-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Final/Ap","inspectorid":"133","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"42539","establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","inspectionDate":"2018-05-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inspectorid":"133","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"5","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"5","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42539","inspectionDate":"5/25/2018","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not smooth and easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth."},{"inspectionid":"42539","inspectionDate":"5/25/2018","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"drain line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"42539","inspectionDate":"5/25/2018","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \r\n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"intake air ducts","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"HOOD","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"inspectionid":"42539","inspectionDate":"5/25/2018","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Ice machine","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"At the AIR GAP","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"inspectionid":"42539","inspectionDate":"5/25/2018","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not spaced to allow access for cleaning","subProblem":"","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate space for cleaning."},{"inspectionid":"42539","inspectionDate":"5/25/2018","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"51622715","name":"Urban Ramen","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622715"}}